Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your time.
Thanks for your hard work.
Amazing.
This day has come, you know.
It's already here.
It's here.
What? It's here.
Stop it. I don't care if it's in another day or something.
I really don't know what to do.
What do you think?
I couldn't sleep.
I did, but in the end...
I couldn't sleep at all.
You did?
But I was a little too sleepy. I was asleep.
I don't know how long I was asleep, but I felt okay.
I felt like something was missing.
Oh, yeah.
I took a bubble bath.
Is that okay?
I put in some bath salts that my makeup artist gave me.
I was going to use it tomorrow.
But I forgot to put in the last one.
You put it in on the way?
Yes, I did.
It was given to me.
I have to use it.
Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, no.
Were you near our room yesterday?
Yes, I was.
Oh, I see.
Did you sing once? A little.
Did you sing?
I was in there, and I heard singing coming from next door, and I was sure it was Carabee's voice.
It was my neighbor.
I don't know if it was next door or close.
Congratulations.
It's the day of the show.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Congratulations.
It's the day.
You all were able to sleep, weren't you?
Did you sleep?
I saw everyone in my dream.
I saw something like an amusement park.
I dreamed that I rented a lip of stone or something.
I had a dream.
Maybe I'll go there.
I think he's coming.
Okay, I'll go this way.
I'll see you for breakfast.
Yikes!
I'd like to chili my breakfast with a base range.
I found this in the dressing room.
What's this?
Good morning.
We'll be on the side today.
Are you guys ready?
Can I open this?
Is it okay if I get in front of the camera?
Here we go.
Ready!
Hito-chan!
Hito-chan's here!
squeak squeak squeak squeak
HITOCHAN'S HITOCHAN! I see... I see...
I was hoping it was a late comer, but...
But I was wrong. It's Hito-chan.
It's Hito-chan!
Cheese ball!
We got a lot of sweet potato gifts yesterday, so I just took out the sweet potato chips,
Then I put this on too.
A sheet mask.
I'm so happy! All the staff members.
Yesterday, too, the makeup artist told me to follow her after the rehearsal,
I got some milky lotion and stuff like that,
Thanks to the sweet potato chips,
Now, thanks to the sweet potato chips,
These are killer!
Pink!
That's so cool!
Haru just looked so cute!
What the hell?
I wonder what it is...
That's something!
Oh, spray!
Hiyori!
Oh my God, it's real!
This is real!
He's so cute!
I'll try the pose.
Stretch out your wrist.
This way.
Your wrists are stretched because you're taking a selfie?
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, spray.
Here.
I haven't put on makeup yet, so it's nice.
You look amazingly pretty.
Pink everywhere.
Pink here, too.
Isn't it nice?
Beautiful.
Trash can.
I'm done with makeup. Good morning. I'm sleepy.
I wanted to go to the CD booth. I'm glad. I won.
I was there.
This is "Mao Chicken Honey".
This honey is good for your health.
They say if you eat a spoon of this every day, you will not catch a cold,
It's Makenori Honey.
In love?
Does it hurt?
Aah!
Solder solder solder solder solder solder solder solder solder solder solder solder
That's enough.
It's over.
Enough! Enough!
That's enough.
Wait a minute.
Your voice...
Looks so delicious!
Thank you for watching!
Happy butter-flavored potato chips!
Lots of baggage!
I'm so happy
I know more people here than I've ever known in my life.
Some of my friends are coming too
I got a call out of the blue saying I was coming over.
I haven't heard from her in a while.
I'm getting calls from friends and people I haven't heard from in a while.
And one girl I hadn't heard from in a really long time.
She said we're going to drive to Koi Park today and have a date.
Like, "Oh my God, I'm going to go to Koi Park.
Koi.
I was like, "Oh my god.
My favorite girl is also coming today.
It's a special date spot, isn't it?
I'm so happy.
Did you just eat it?
Really?
He's not a potato master.
But you're a potato master.
The texture is unusual for a potato.
Give me a break.
LOL!
Laughing.
What?
I made a perfect mistake.
I wrote it in youth. Are you having fun in your youth?
This is for tomorrow.
I've been working on it since the day before. I made a mistake.
It was love.
Are you enjoying your youth?
Where are you?
Uma.
Isn't my house great?
We had a party today.
Oh, my God!
Oh, he's so cute!
He's so cute!
She's so cute!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, wow!
Oh, my gosh! It's our own show!
Isn't it amazing?
I want to make this a regular thing.
Every time. If we take it slow every time, I'm sure we can do it.
Maybe one day we can come to the candy store.
The candy maker said it's a surprise.
The sea urchins are all very nervous.
Oh, it looks so good!
Looks delicious! I'm so happy! Warm rice.
Let's give it to mom! School lunch! Just like school lunch!
I just got a massage from the doctor, so I feel super energized.
Fold your elbows in, curve up to your chest, and arch your back.
Don't let it interfere with your hair.
I just got my nails stitched. So pretty! So sparkly!
For Love Park.
Yes, I love you. Love KANAMI more.
Yes, I wrote it. Who will receive this?
Heart because of love. Today.
Heh heh heh. Ehh~.
The nails are cute. Glossy.
Yes, it's over.
It looks like there are already some publicity staff outside the venue.
It looks like they already came very early in the morning.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
What's the big deal? Tomorrow.
Don't remind me what's so important. I've only seen it today.
Come on, let's all go together.
Thank you.
It's cold. It's cold.
Bible! Thank you very much.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
It's the first day of the Yokohama Arena show.
Please be safe.
Let me greet you together.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
To the hearts of all the staff.
LONG LONG LONG LONG
We, the Publicity Department of Super Time, look forward to working with you.
Please give us your best regards.
Please take care of us.
We had a full rehearsal yesterday.
I'd like to do a quick rehearsal today and go to the show.
It's been a year and a month since the announcement.
Finally, we are going to perform today.
I thought there were many more years to go.
So it's been quite busy.
I've been busy, I guess.
That's why
I think today will probably go by very quickly.
I want to enjoy this moment that comes only once.
I'm really looking forward to the scenery.
We've been rehearsing at the venue since yesterday.
I thought it was really big and stretched out horizontally.
So when I think about the publicity staff gathering there
I'm really excited to see what the view will be like.
It really took a lot of work to get here.
I don't know.
There have been a lot of times when things haven't gone as well as I'd hoped.
I wonder if we're going to be successful
I wonder if we are going to be successful
There were times when I was worried
There were times when all the members talked about it together.
But all of you believed in us at all times.
We are confident that we can do it.
I think that's why we have been able to see such a beautiful view this time.
I think we will be able to see a beautiful view this time.
I believe that we will be able to see a beautiful view this time.
I would like to do my best to make our performance on the stage
I will do my best to make the stage and the performance that will make you feel that what you have done so far has not yet been enough.
It looks like I will be able to start the first day without any problems.
It's been a while since I've sung in a one-man show.
That's it.
I'm really nervous about the fact that it will be the largest capacity one-man live concert I've ever done.
I'm really nervous.
I'm so nervous, I'm so nervous, I'm so nervous.
I'm so excited, but I'm really looking forward to it.
The audience is already here.
Come here.
They're here, they're here, they're here, they're here, they're here! There are so many!
I saw some people.
No, no, no, they're looking.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to be exposed.
I'm assuming we can film each person for one minute.
Mr. Oh, I found a toy.
Oh, boy, I found a toy.
Good day, see you later.
Today's, today's, today's, that half-twin is so cute!
That half-twin is so cute!
That's what I want in the future.
I like the height and the amount of food it takes up...
And the outer wings.
Let's do it this way.
Oh, the outer feather.
That's cute.
I see.
I'll tell the makeup artist.
It's cute, sir.
It's like an educational program.
It's because of Kanami's voice.
I wonder why
Miki is like this
Hiyorin's voice
It's a perfect fit.
She talked so much.
Thank you for the rehearsal. Please take care of the performance.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the first day.
Please take care of us.
Thank you very much.
Please, please, please.
Something smells good.
It smells like sesame dumplings.
Look!
What?
What is it?
Wow!
I got some Kiyoke cheese, gold medals, and shrimp.
Have you ever had gold medal and cheese?
Cheese!
Let's fix your makeup.
I got a gold medal and a shrimp with cheese from Chiyouke's shumai.
It's so gorgeous. I'll have some.
Oh!
Oh no!
I bet everyone is having this reaction.
While having them attacked.
I'm so happy.
Was I getting horny?
Well, I'll take a picture too.
I'm getting a feeling of cheese popularity.
It's so hot.
Whenever I go to Osaka...
I get steamed meat buns.
The ones in the chilled bag.
I'm so happy.
Sprinkle some on.
Did you take a picture?
Not yet.
You haven't taken it yet?
No, I haven't.
Then I'd like to have some.
Why are you crying, doctor?
Yes, sir.
Nuh-uh.
Okay, then
All of you
Wait here for a minute.
Let's go!
preview of next episode
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday.
And on the canvas of our broken hearts, they paint a piece of the future to guide us.
I can say it now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye, good bye, yesterday's me
After the rain, the town, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools and sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, Good bye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, the city, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling clouds of tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!